# Tran, Le Anh (1996)

"Once the WHY is clear, the HOW goes easy"

Seoul, South Korea 🔀 tranleanh.nt@gmail.com

tranleanh.github.io in /in/tranleanh

#### ABOUT ME -

I completed my PhD under the guidance of Prof. Dong-Chul Park in early 2024, marking an important milestone in my research journey. I specialize in **Python** programming and have experience with various frameworks such as **tensorflow**, **pytorch**, **conda**, etc. My publications have mainly revolved around **image enhancement**, **cluster analysis**, and **object detection**. I am also a writer for popular Medium publications such as **Towards Data Science**, **Level Up Coding**, etc.

### **EDUCATION** -

3/2021 - 2/2024 **PhD in Computer Vision** 

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

3/2019 - 2/2021 **MSc in Computer Vision** 

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

9/2014 - 8/2018 BEng in Automation and Control Engineering (graduated with honors)

HCMC University of Technology and Education (HCMUTE), Vietnam

### EXPERIENCE -

4/2020 - Present Research Staff Member

MindinTech, Inc., Seoul, South Korea

Researched and developed vision-based techniques for advanced driver-assistance systems

3/2021 - 2/2024 **Research Assistant** 

Intelligent Computing Research Lab (ICRL), Myongji University, South Korea

Researched and developed cutting-edge algorithms for image enhancement and cluster analysis

7/2019 - 9/2019 Software Development Intern

OCST Co., Ltd., Seoul, South Korea

Developed a software system for object detection streaming and data management

3/2018 - 2/2019 Al Engineer

FPT Software, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Developed and implemented vision-based algorithms for the first piloted driver-less car in Vietnam

2/2017 - 1/2018 **Teaching Assistant** 

Faculty of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, HCMUTE, Vietnam

Assisted the lecturer during classes, prepared lesson plans, and evaluated assignments

## **EXPERTISE**

# Skills

- Programming: Python, Conda, Darknet, Tensorflow, Keras, Pytorch
- Document Presentation: MS Word, MS PowerPoint, LaTeX
- Technical: Statistical Analysis, Visualization, Technical Reporting, Problem Solving, etc.
- Concept: Knowledge Distillation, Knowledge Transfer, Learning without Forgetting, Dark Channel Prior, Non-Maximum Suppression, Vision Transformer, Generative Adversarial Networks, etc.

# Languages

- Vietnamese (native)
- English (proficient)

## **Activities**

- IEEE Member
- IEEE Young Professional
- Reviewer for SCIE Journals (IEEE Transactions on Image Processing, Intelligent Data Analysis)

PUBLICATIONS	
2024	<b>POCS-based Image Compression: An Empirical Examination</b> TD Do $^{\nabla}$ , LA Tran $^{\nabla}$ , TD Nguyen, NN Truong, DC Park, MH Le
	IEEE International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD)
2024	Encoder-Decoder Networks with Guided Transmission Map for Effective Image Dehazing
	LA Tran, DC Park The Visual Computer, Springer ( <b>SCIE</b> )
2024	Cluster Analysis via Projection onto Convex Sets
2024	LA Tran, D Kwon, HM Deberneh, DC Park
	Intelligent Data Analysis, IOS Press ( <b>SCIE</b> )
2024	Toward Improving Robustness of Object Detectors against Domain Shift LA $Tran^{\nabla}$ , NC $Tran^{\nabla}$ , DC Park, J Carrabina, D Castells-Rufas
	IEEE International Conference on Green Energy, Computing and Sustainable Technology (GECOST)
2024	Single Image Dehazing via Regional Saturation-Value Translation
	LA Tran, D Kwon, DC Park Procedia Computer Science, Vol. 237
2023	Embedding Clustering via Autoencoder and Projection onto Convex Set
2023	LA Tran, TD Nguyen, TD Do, NC Tran, D Kwon, DC Park
	IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2023	<b>Efficient Infrared-Thermal Imaging Fusion for Human Detection in Heavy Smoke Scenarios</b> NN Truong, MH Le, TD Do, LA Tran, TD Nguyen, HH Trinh
	IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2023	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Robustness and Applicability
	LA Tran, DC Park Smart Innovation, Systems and Technologies, Vol. 333
2022	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Architecture
2022	LA Tran, DC Park
	International Conference on Advances in Signal Processing and Artificial Intelligence (ASPAI)
2022	POCS-based Clustering Algorithm LA Tran, HM Deberneh, TD Do, TD Nguyen, MH Le, DC Park
	IEEE International Workshop on Intelligent Systems (IWIS)
2022	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map for Image Dehazing
	LA Tran, S Moon, DC Park Procedia Computer Science, Vol. 204
2021	Enhancement of Robustness in Object Detection Module for ADAS
	LA Tran, TD Do, DC Park, MH Le IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2222	,
2020	Object Detection Streaming and Data Management on Web Browser  LA Tran
	Technical Report, OCST Co., Ltd.
2019	Robust U-Net-based Road Lane Markings Detection for Autonomous Driving LA Tran, MH Le
	IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2018	A Vision-based Method for Autonomous Landing on a Target with a Quadcopter
	LA Tran, NP Le, TD Do, MH Le IEEE International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD)
Lindor Doviovy	
Under Review	<b>Efficient Big Data Analysis via POCS and Centroid Neural Network</b> LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Distilled Pooling Transformer Encoder for Efficient Realistic Image Dehazing
	LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Haze Removal via Regional Saturation-Value Translation and Soft Segmentation

LA Tran, DC Park

**Soft Knowledge-based Distilled Dehazing Networks** LA Tran, DC Park Under Review

Clustering Optimization via Centroid Neural Network Ensemble NC Tran $^{\nabla}$ , LA Tran $^{\nabla}$ , DC Park, J Carrabina, D Castells-Rufas Under Review

 $\nabla\!\!:$  equal contribution